你怎么没睡?
Why are you up?
我怎么睡得着?
How am I supposed to sleep?
我才刚结婚不到24小时
I've been married less than 24 hours,
我老婆就不跟我说话了
and my wife isn't speaking to me.
也许你应该想想这事儿好的一面
Perhaps you can think of this in a more positive light.
你花了一天就体验完了
In one day, you've managed to do
其他夫妇花几十年才完成的事情
what it takes many couples decades to achieve.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你也睡不着吗?
You couldn't sleep either?
当然睡不着
Of course not.
我也是
Me neither.
但我只是喉咙有点痒
But I just had a tickle in my throat.
不是因为严重的婚姻问题
Not profound marital problems.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
请告诉我该怎么解决
Please, tell me how I can fix it.
幸亏你问了
Glad you asked.
在我看来 有个很简单的解决办法
As I see it, there's a simple solution.
你的嘴唇调戏过别的女人的嘴唇
Your lips had a dalliance with the lips of another woman.
要想恢复你们关系的平衡
It seems only logical that
你应该另找个男人
to restore balance to the relationship,
调戏一下 这样才合乎逻辑
you should find another man and dally with him.
我说的"调戏"是指激烈的
And by dally, I mean some hardcore
嘴对嘴运动
mouth-on-mouth action.
好吧 那是我听过最蠢的主意
Okay, that is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
其实 我觉得他说对了
Actually, I think he's onto something.
你... 在开玩笑吧
Y... You can't be serious.
因为我以前鬼混 和一个妹子亲了嘴
'Cause I messed up and made out with a girl,
你就要随便找个汉子也亲一口?
you're gonna do the same with a random guy?
我目前单身
I'm currently single.
没错 你的确单身
That's true. You are.
搞什么呢?!
What is happening?!
我来告诉你这是搞什么
I will tell you what is happening.
我在挽救最好朋友的婚姻
I am saving my best friend's marriage.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第2集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酱油影  时间轴: 奥利奥
校对: UUUUUU
翻译: 酱油影 猫呗 夏至未寒 小黄不小黄
Sheldon 我觉得你不明白
Sheldon, I don't think you understand
分手应该是什么状态
how being broken up works.
唯一能让我理清情绪的方式
The only way I can sort through my feelings
就是我俩保持距离
is if there is space between us.
我每次看到你 又会再受一次伤
Every time I see you, it re-traumatizes me.
又得重复经历同样的痛苦
I go through the pain all over again.
我也向你问好
Well, hello to you, too.
你想怎样?
What do you want?
我明白我们已经不是情侣
I understand we're no longer a couple,
但我想提醒你 我们一起造过小孩
but I would like to remind you that we made a baby together.
什么小孩?
What baby?
一个早熟的网络小节目
A precocious little Internet show
名为"旗乐无穷"
known as "Fun With Flags."
我要挂了
I'm hanging up.
好 我们半小时后见
Great. See you in about half an hour.
Sheldon 我不会和你一起主持"旗乐无穷"的
Sheldon, I am not doing "Fun With Flags" with you.
为什么?
Why not?
因为我们分手了
Because we're broken up.
桑尼和雪儿就行
Sonny and Cher made it work.
美国著名夫妻档歌手 后离婚
他们离婚很久之后
Their variety show kept going
还是继续同台演出
long after the divorce,
我们至今还在谈论他们
and here we are still talking about them.
没人会说起桑尼和雪儿
No one's talking about Sonny and Cher.
你肯定是错想成了唐尼和玛丽那对
You must be thinking about Donny and Marie,
但我们在说的绝对是桑尼和雪儿
'cause you and I are clearly talking about Sonny and Cher.
Sheldon 不能这么下去了
Sheldon, this has to stop.
我知道这很难
I know it's hard.
对我来说也是
It's hard for me, too.
但我们分手后这两天
But I've seen and talked to you more
我们见面和交谈的次数
in the two days we've been broken up
比分手前两个月的都要多
than in the last two months that we were together.
好吧 如果你想少看到我
Well, if you want to see less of me,
也许我们应该在一起
maybe we should go out again.
真是难以置信 你和Mandy Chao亲嘴了
I can't believe you made out with Mandy Chao.
相信我 我希望我没那么干
Trust me, I wish it never happened.
你一直就知道这件事?
And you knew about this this whole time?
对
I did.
你还没想着告诉我?
And you didn't think to tell me?
Leonard让我不要说出去的
Leonard asked me to keep it to myself.
我们暂时先不要提Leonard
Let's leave Leonard out of this for the moment.
这是我们之间的事
This is about you and me.
等等 等等 我和老婆的新婚危机
Wait, wait, wait, how is my day-old marriage falling apart
怎么就成你俩的事了?
becoming about you two?
等等
Hang on.
我该做什么才能赢得你的信任?
What do I need to do to make you trust me?
你觉得有一个老婆日子就艰难了
You think it's hard having one wife,
试试看两个
try having two.
我打赌你肯定告诉Bernadette
I bet you told Bernadette
他和Mandy Chao各种厮混的事情了
all about he was screwing around with Mandy Chao.
我们没有厮混
Oh, we didn't screw around.
我们只是喝醉了 亲了个嘴
We just got drunk and made out.
随便了 要是你告诉我 我会舒服很多
Whatever. It would have been nice to hear it from you.
你来这做什么?
What are you doing here?
我是来把东西还给你的
I'm here to return your belongings.
大家分手后都会这么做
That's what people who've broken up do.
而且你还没用惯用的敲门方式
And you didn't do your compulsive knocking ritual
所以我才会开门
so I would open the door.
反而言之
On the contrary,
你再也没法享受我那魅力十足的怪癖
you no longer get to enjoy my charming eccentricities.
我们不是有福利的朋友
We're not friends with benefits.
把盒子给我
Just give me the box.
等... 等等 难道你不想翻看一下
W... Wait. Don't you want to go through it
确保我没把什么东西落下吗?
to make sure I haven't forgotten anything?
行吧
Fine.
我的旧围巾
My old scarf.
那晚你带着它和我一起去溜冰 记得吗?
You wore it the night we went ice-skating. Remember?
你是说我一人在溜冰
You mean the night that I went ice-skating,
而你站在扶手栏杆边
and you stood at the rail
谷歌体温过低症状的那晚?
Googling the symptoms of hypothermia?
咱们合作多愉快啊 是咩?
We made one heck of a team, huh?
这是谁的罩罩?
Whose bra is this?
这不是你的?
It's not yours?
哎呀呀
Oh, my.
这也太尴尬了
How embarrassing for both of us.
这是Penny的
It's Penny's.
嘿 你已经和我分手了
Hey, you broke up with me.
我乐意去揉搓谁那一团
It is none of your business
裸露的胸部 和你无关
whose naked bosom I'm smooshing around like pizza dough.
再见
Good-bye.
Amy开门
Amy.
Amy开门 Amy开门
Amy. Amy.
嗯 桌子也能起作用
Hmm. Tables work, too.
真不错
Good to know.
你为女孩之夜做了布朗尼蛋糕!
Ooh, brownies for girls' night!
把手拿开 我在生你的气
Hands off. I'm mad at you.
听着 我知道我花了一大笔钱
Look, I know it's a lot of money,
但是店里那人说
but the guy at the store said
大概过个五六年 这东西会自己涨价的
in five to seven years, it'll pay for itself.
什么东西会自己涨价?
What will pay for itself?
没什么 你生我什么气呢?
Doesn't matter. What are you mad about?
我气你告诉我
I'm mad at you for blabbing to me
Leonard在北海做的那些事
what Leonard did on the North Sea,
所以这两年里
and I'm mad that I've had to hide this
我都要向Penny瞒着这事
from Penny for two years.
你因为这事生气是应该的
And you have every right to be mad about those things.
不如 你把这个月的信用卡账单
So, why don't you let me
给我来保管 怎么样?
handle the credit card bill this month, huh?
就不劳烦你看了
I mean, don't even look at it.
我是说 假如Penny知道了这么久以来
I mean, if Penny finds out I've known all this time
我都瞒着她
and haven't told her,
她就会觉得我这个朋友不值得交
she's gonna think I'm a terrible friend.
要是你没告诉我就好了
I wish you never told me.
要是Leonard没告诉我才好呢
And I wish Leonard never told me.
他做错事 他才是坏人
He's the bad guy here.
你说的对
I guess that's true.
而你却让Penny嫁给了他
And you let Penny marry him.
对比这事 我买了一个乔治克鲁尼的
Compared to that, who cares if I bought
限量版体毛修剪套件又算得上什么呢?
a George Clooney limited edition manscaping kit?
您好 我打电话想了解一下你们婚姻咨询服务
Hi. I'm calling about your marriage counseling services
也想问一下费用怎么计
and was curious what your rate is.
你是在逗我
Really?
好吧
Um, okay.
结婚不久有没有折扣打?
Is there any kind of discount for length of marriage?
因为也就结了那么几十小时
'Cause we're just talking hours here.
- 嗨  - 等会打给你
- Hi.  - Call you back.
嘿
Hey.
我们能谈谈吗?
Can we talk?
我很乐意
I would love that.
好的 听着
All right, look,
我对我结婚之前说一切都没问题
I'm sorry I said I was okay with everything
这事感到很抱歉
before we got married.
我很讨厌我们现在这个状态
I hate that we're going through this,
但是我又不知道该怎么办
but I don't know what to do.
你要是不介意上团购排队抢票
If you don't mind waiting for a Groupon,
我们可以试试婚姻咨询
we can try marriage counseling.
哈喽
Hello.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, uh, buddy,
可以给我们空间单独谈话吗?
can we have some privacy?
当然可以
Oh, of course.
不会打扰你们
Wouldn't want to intrude.
这是你的
This is yours.
好的 等我和他说完
Okay, when I'm done with him,
我要你给我解释清楚
I'm gonna need more information.
没什么大不了的
Nothing odd.
只不过想用来气Amy罢了
I just wanted to rub Amy's nose in it.
好了 我知道我可能反应过激了
Okay, look, I might be overreacting,
但是一想到你明天
but how am I supposed to get past this
去工作就要见到这个女人
when I know tomorrow you're gonna go to work
你让我怎么忍受的了?
and see this woman?
请原谅我偷听了
Forgive me for eavesdropping,
但是依我看 有个简单的解决办法
but as I see it, there's a simple solution.
醒醒 快醒醒 快醒醒
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
带Penny去见Mandy
Bring Penny to meet Mandy.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
目前为止 Penny难以控制她的想象
Well, right now, Penny's imagination is running wild,
但是假如见面了 神秘感消失
but if they meet, that will eliminate
她的担忧也会减少
the mystery and alleviate her fears.
就像卖斯帕克林矿泉水的那个人让我掀开了他的眼罩
Like when that Sparkletts guy let me look under his eye patch.
首先 你把他气哭了
Uh, first of all, you made that guy cry.
然后我们就知道了 没有眼球也是可以哭的
And we learned that you don't need an eyeball to do that.
第二 我觉得Penny和Mandy见面这主意
Secondly, I can't think of a more horrible idea
实在太糟糕了
than Penny meeting Mandy.
是吗? 为什么这么说?
Really? Why is that?
你真的想见她吗?
What, you actually want to meet her?
本来不想 看你现在遮遮掩掩的
No, but now that you're being weird about it,
也许我就该见见
maybe I should.
我没有遮遮掩掩
I'm not being weird.
我有遮掩吗?
Am I being weird?
有
Yes.
这种感觉我都看出来了
And that's coming from me.
好吧 你想去见她?
Fine, you want to meet her?
不 我就是想确认你们工作的时候
No, I just want to know that when you're at work,
什么事都不会发生
there's nothing going on.
要和你说多少次你才能信?
How many times do I have to tell you?
我对这个女人没有兴趣
I have no interest in this woman.
那也有可能是她对你有兴趣啊
Yeah, well, maybe she has interest in you.
对Leonard有兴趣?
In Leonard?
连那个卖矿泉水的都知道这事根本不可能
Oh, even the Sparkletts guy could see that's unlikely.
我觉得最大的问题是
I guess my big problem is I never saw Leonard
我没想到Leonard竟会做出这种事情来
as the kind of guy who would do something like this.
人总会在软弱的时候犯错误
Anybody can make a mistake in a weak moment.
你怎么想呢?
What do you think?
呃 我不知道该怎么想
Oh, I don't know what to think.
但是我再强调一遍 我也是刚刚才知道
But then again, I just found out about it.
你知道的 我之所以爱上Leonard
You know, I fell in love with Leonard
就是因为他和我之前约过的那些男人
because he wasn't anything like the guys
完全不一样
I was used to dating.
我知道以前那些男的劈腿劈惯了
I mean, I knew those guys weren't above cheating
因为通常劈的就是我
because that's usually how we met.
拜托 你知道Leonard不是这样的人
Come on, you know Leonard's not like that.
我特别想相信你 真的
I want to believe you. I really do.
我是不是很幼稚啊?
Am I being naive?
呃 我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
这些都超出了我理解范围
This is all so new to me.
我还在消化
I'm still processing.
你知道的 他第一次见我的时候 可绝不会做这种事
You know, he never would've done this when we first met.
他现在胆子大了
He's cockier now.
那是因为你让他有信心了
That's because you made him more confident.
想想看 如果没有你
You know, if you think about it, without you,
他也不会成为现在的他
he never would've grown into the person he is now.
说真心的 更多美女会注意到他
I mean, sure, more women might notice him,
但我觉得他和你在一起更好
but I think it's better to have a guy be with you
因为他想和你一起
because he wants to be
而不是因为 他除了你别无选择
and not because he thinks he doesn't have any other choice.
我从来不这么想
I never thought about it like that.
呃 我也是 刚刚才想到的
Oh, me neither, not until just now.
大家好 我是Sheldon Cooper博士
Hello. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
欢迎来到 "Sheldon Cooper出品: 旗乐无穷"
and welcome to "Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun With Flags".
大家可能已经注意到了 我拿了一个遥控器
You may notice that I'm holding a remote control.
那是因为我的摄影师兼主持搭档
That's because my cameraperson and co-host,
Amy Farrah Fowler博士
Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler,
已经决定终止我们之间的关系
has chosen to end her relationship with me.
我暂停一下 好让你们消化一下
I'm going to pause here to let that sink in.
好的
Okay.
如果你想让暂停更长一点
If you need to pause a little longer,
请摁暂停键
just click the pause button.
当然 节目必须继续
But the show must go on.
还有 我只需用一只右手
And thankfully, all the things my girlfriend used to do
就能完全代替我女朋友
can be taken care of with my right hand.
好了 别浪费时间说她了
Anyway, let's not spend any more time talking about her.
我们是来说旗子的
We're here to talk about flags.
今晚的主题是:
Tonight's theme:
心碎国家的旗帜
flags of countries that have been torn apart
与一个我认为应该对此负责的女人
and the women I have a feeling were responsible.
你们知道去找一个婚姻咨询师
You guys have any idea how much it costs
要花多少钱吗?
to see a marriage counselor?
250刀一小时 问这个干嘛?
$250 an hour. Why?
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
我和Bernadette曾经去过一次
Bernadette and I have occasionally gone to one to,
你懂得 要保持爱情的感觉
you know, stay on top of things.
然后你现在才告诉我?
And I'm just hearing about this now?
兄弟 虽然我们是最好的朋友
Dude, just because we're best friends
但是这不代表我得把什么都告诉你啊
doesn't mean that I have to tell you everything that goes on.
不是必须告诉我 而是你应该想着告诉我
You don't have to, you should want to.
得了 Mandy过来了
Oh, great, there's Mandy.
为什么海洋生物学家都漂亮?
Why are marine biologists always so cute?
不知道
I don't know,
不过我愿意迷失在她的百慕大三角里
but I'd like to get lost in her Bermuda Triangle.
说这个有卵用
That's not helpful.
那我不会说
Then I won't say
我想趴在她四分之三的表面上
I'd like to cover three-quarters of her surface area.
你们够了没有?
Are we done?
还没 这个太有意思了
Not yet, this is fun.
噢 我有了
Ooh, I know.
我想让她帮我放松一下老二
I'd let her free my willy.
你干嘛去?
Where you going?
我想问问她 是否愿意见见Penny
I'm gonna ask her if she'd be willing to talk to Penny,
告诉她 我们之间没什么好担心的
tell her she has nothing to worry about.
- 等等 Leonard  - 怎么?
- Leonard, wait.  - What?
我想把她的海绵裤剪碎
I'd like to SpongeBob her SquarePants.
现在我们够了
Now we are done.
嘿
Hey.
嗨 Leonard 怎么了?
Oh, hi, Leonard. What's up?
呃 我坐下你不介意吧?
Uh, do you mind if I sit?
当然
Sure.
呃 我一直在想我们俩
So, um, I've been thinking a lot
还有... 船上的事
about you and me and... the boat.
想这个干嘛?
What about it?
你知道的...
You know...
当时我们喝醉了以后做的事
what we did, when we were drunk.
呃 那天我也睡了你吗?
Oh, no, did I sleep with you, too?
没有 我们亲了而已
No, we just made out.
噢 那就好
Oh. Well, good for me.
有什么能为你做的吗?
So what can I do for you?
呃 是这样的 我最近结婚了
Uh, okay, well, um, I got married recently.
噢 恭喜!
Oh, congratulations!
和Sheldon吗?
To Sheldon?
还是一样好笑啊
Never gets old.
不是的 和一个女孩儿
No, no, to a girl.
呃 我跟她说了我们之间的事情
Anyway, I told her what happened between you and me,
她很担心 因为我们在工作中总是碰面
and she's concerned about us seeing each other at work.
就是亲了一下而已 你干嘛告诉她?
It was just a kiss. Why would you even tell her?
因为我不想跟她之间有秘密
Because I didn't want there to be any secrets between us.
真的是因为这个吗?
Is that really the reason?
还能是因为什么?
What else would it be?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
听上去好像你要毁了这段关系了
Sounds like you're trying to sabotage the relationship.
不会 我不这么觉得
No, I don't think so.
虽然 Penny说的跟你说的一模一样
Although, Penny did say exactly that.
呃 那你就应该好好想想了
Okay, well, that's something to think about.
你知道的 有时候 我觉得
You know, on some level, I've always believed
我配不上她这样一个女孩儿
that I don't deserve a woman like her.
呃 你打算就在这儿想这个么?
Oh, you're gonna think about that right here?
她真的很漂亮
I mean, she's really beautiful.
世上的男人她想拥有谁都可以
She could have any guy she wants.
她花了那么多年
Which is probably why
才和我说她爱我估计也是这个原因
it took her so many years to tell me she loved me.
也许你应该去找个心理医生谈一谈
Maybe you should talk to a therapist about this.
太贵了
Too expensive.
我应该是很习惯女人在对我表达感情的时候有所保留的
You'd think I'd be used to women withholding their love.
我妈就是这样
I mean, my mother did.
不管我多努力
I mean, no matter how hard I tried,
她都对我一点兴趣也没有
she just didn't have any interest in me.
真是没法想象
Imagine that.
不知道这是不是为什么
I wonder if that's why I have
我和Sheldon之间有那么不正常的关系
such a dysfunctional relationship with Sheldon.
我做了一个梦
I had a dream
我在一个山洞里
the other night that I was in a cave
我在照顾一个婴儿
and I was nursing a baby,
但是那个婴儿的头是Sheldon的
but the baby had Sheldon's head on it.
你妻子还担心我?
And your wife is worried about me?
嘿 Leonard!
Hey, Leonard!
你谈完了过来
When you're done,
我们又想出了好多
we came up with a bunch more.
然后捷克共和国对斯洛伐克说
Then the Czech Republic says to Slovakia,
"我觉得你根本不懂分手是什么意思!"
"I don't think you understand how being broken up works!"
你能相信吗?
Can you believe that?
按常理说捷克共和国
You'd think that the Czech Republic
应该会珍惜自己所拥有的东西
would try to hold on to what it had,
因为它已经不像以前那么年轻了
given that it's not as young as it used to be.
而且我也没见什么别的国家
And I don't see any other countries
排着队从南边对它的边境发起进攻啊
lining up to invade its southern borders.
我要把他杀了
I'm gonna kill him.
不说捷克共和国了
But enough about the Czech Republic.
有一次摩尔多瓦给罗马尼亚
Let's talk about the time Moldova made Romania
做了一个生日蛋糕 罗马尼亚说那个蛋糕很好吃
a birthday cake and Romania said it tasted good
但其实它一点都不好吃
even though it didn't.
但是罗马尼亚还是被甩了
And yet Romania gets dumped.
我现在暂停 让你们反应一下
I'll pause here while you mull that one over.
我说呢 对吧?
I know, right?
你说你有话想对我说
So, you said you had something to tell me.
好的 是的 嗯
Okay, yeah, um,
你记得你说我
do you remember when you accused me
想故意破坏我们的婚姻吗?
of trying to sabotage our wedding?
嗯
Uh-huh.
我想了很久 你可能说对了
I've been thinking about it, and you might be right.
但是好在我觉得我知道这是为什么
But the good news is that I'm pretty sure I know why.
继续说
I'm listening.
Penny 这么多年了
Penny, after all these years,
我还是感觉也许我配不上你
I still feel like maybe I don't deserve you.
好吧 这是全天下
Okay, that is the lamest excuse
最差劲的借口了
you could've possibly come up with.
但我懂
But I get it.
真的?
You do?
是啊
Yeah.
有时候我害怕你会有一天
Sometimes I worry you're gonna wake up
离开我去和一个更像你的人在一起
and leave me for someone more like you.
我连你为什么会和我这种人在一起都不知道
I don't even understand why you're with someone like me.
我怎么会想和我这种人在一起?
Why would I want to be with someone like me?
你知道我的意思的
You know what I mean.
而且 也许我对这件事情的反应
And, you know, maybe the way I've been reacting
也是在破坏我们的婚姻
was me sabotaging this, too.
我们能不能不再这样
Well, how about we stop
害怕失去对方
being so scared of losing each other
好好在一起呢?
and just be together?
听上去不错
That sounds nice.
真好
Good.
因为...
Because...
我第一次见到你就爱上你了
I've loved you since the moment we met,
我会一直爱你 直到海枯石烂
and I will keep loving you until the end of time.
哦
Oh.
天啊 这是我听过的
Oh, my God, that is the most beautiful thing
- 最美的话了  - 是吗?
- anyone's ever said to me.  - Yeah?
那是因为你很美
That's because you're beautiful,
你的美浇灌着我的心田
and your beauty fills my heart with love and song.
现在有点肉麻了吧 Leonard
It's getting kind of cheesy, Leonard.
额?
Huh?
如果你觉得这肉麻的话 忍着点
If you think that's cheesy, buckle up.
Penny Hofstadter啊
Penny Hofstadter,
你愿意继续做我的妻子吗?
will you please stay married to me?
妈的 你太强了
Oh, damn it, you topped it.
我们要不要去卧室里把这场婚礼正式办完啊?
Should we go to the bedroom and make this marriage official?
- 要!  - 好的!
- Yes, please!  - Okay!
Sheldon 真不敢相信你给我们了一份结婚礼物
Sheldon, I can't believe you got us a wedding gift.
真不知道你们那么吃惊干什么
I don't know why you're so surprised.
我也看电影的 我知道人们通常会做什么
I watch movies; I see what people do.
这是什么?
What is this?
旧金山周末游的
Plane tickets and hotel reservations
机票和酒店预订
for a weekend away in San Francisco.
哦! 哇!
Oh! Wow!
太棒了!
That's so great!
是啊 有渔人码头 恶魔岛 还有缆车
Yeah, there's Fisherman's Wharf and Alcatraz and cable cars.
我们一定能玩得很开心的
We're gonna have so much fun.
我们?
We?
有问题吗?
Is there a problem?
哦 没有! 我刚刚说的是"太棒了!"
Oh, no, no! I just, I said, "Whee!"
你竟敢在网上说我坏话
How dare you go on the Internet and say mean things about me
还把我的生殖器比作捷克斯洛伐克的一个地区?!
and compare my genitalia to part of Czechoslovakia?!
你把那集看完了 是吗?
You saw through that one, did you?
我真不知道你在想什么
I don't know what you were thinking,
但你给我把那个视频撤下来!
but take the video down now!
她看了
She watched it.
我能把她追回来的
I'm gonna get that girl back.
我看了是因为你把它用邮件发给我了
I only watched it because you e-mailed it to me
标题还写了"你看了这个肯定会生气"!
with the subject line: "This is gonna make you mad"!
她在门外听我说话 她想要我
She was listening through the door. She wants me.